In this video you will know
how much salary a Scenery Manager gets in ICC Bank.
This is a big post. When you gain
experience of many years, then you
become a Scenery Manager. So this salary
data is best for you.
163 people have told their salaries on this
platform. According to that, the
average salary that has been calculated for you is
2 million per year, that is, 20 lakhs, which
you get per year as a Scenery Manager. And the
average additional pay that you can get separately,
yearly like bonus, you can take incentive,
it has been shown to you here.
You can get ₹350 thousand separately as bonus and
residency here.
Right on this post, you will see the salary structure of Scenery
Manager in ICC Bank. If you liked the video, then
like and subscribe.